Customer Service Menu

##### [Help Center](https://www.landsend.com/customer-service/)

* * *

LANDS’ END PRIVACY POLICY
=========================

### Effective October 18, 2023

This website (“Site”) is owned and operated by Lands’ End‚ Inc. or an affiliated entity. The goal of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the information we gather about you‚ how we use and share that information‚ and how we safeguard that information.

Your use of this Site‚ and any disputes arising from it‚ are subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all its dispute resolution provisions‚ including arbitration‚ class action waiver‚ limitation on damages‚ and choice of law. We may change or add to this privacy policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically. Your continued use of this Site following such changes demonstrates your consent to them.

Below is a summary of the categories of personal information we collect, where we get it, why we collect it, and to whom we may disclose it:

| **CATEGORY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION** | **SOURCE OF INFORMATION** | **PURPOSE FOR COLLECTION** | **CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS** |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Identification and contact information:** such as your name and surname, title, unique personal identifier, online identifier, location, password, postal address, email address, telephone numbers, or other contact details and information you may provide to us when you register or update an account; sign up for email communications; participate in a contest, sweepstakes, promotion or survey; join our mailing list; request a catalog; shop online; or shop by telephone or in stores | From you (online and offline, such as in stores/in the course of using or processing online services or remote order/sales services, including chatting online with or otherwise contacting customer service) | To communicate with you about your orders or purchases, your account, a contest or sweepstakes you have entered, and your requests for information; to enable you to access our services; to provide customer support in response to your communications with us; to send you updates about new products and offers that may be of interest to you; to process your application for a Lands’ End credit card; to tailor your experience at our Site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in; and to communicate with you in the event of product alerts or information including product recalls | With related entities; with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.); and with your consent, with third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you |
| **Information you provide about a third party:** name, surname, address, and contact details of recipient for delivery of goods or services (such as sending a gift or virtual gift card), if different from yours | From you | To complete a particular transaction or fulfill a service | With related entities and with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.) |
| **Purchase and order information:** billing and shipping addresses, together with purchase details (products, color, size, quantity, price), methods of payment and/or any communications we have received about your order or purchase | From you or from a customer who places an order to be delivered to you | To complete a particular transaction or fulfill a service; to validate, confirm, verify, deliver, install, and track your order, including to arrange for shipping and handle returns and refunds; to provide customer service; to maintain a record of the purchases you make, to service products you purchased from us, and to provide you offers that may be of interest to you or to assist with account credit or fraud decisioning; and to communicate with you in the event of product alerts or information including product recalls | With related entities; with certain authorized third parties that process, fulfill, and ship orders; and with our credit partners |
| **Payment card information:** such as name, card issuer and card type, credit or debit card number, expiration date, CVV code, billing addresses, and other financial information shared when making a purchase | From you | To complete a particular transaction or fulfill a service; to check that the right person is using the right card or account; to meet the requirements of the card brands or account issuers; to make sure we are paid for what you buy; and to process your application for a Lands’ End credit card | Our card processor stores all credit card information. It conducts the credit card transactions using commercially reasonable security precautions, controls, policies, and procedures consistent with generally accepted data processing standards in the financial services industry. We only store a record that the transaction took place and the amount you paid in connection with your account information. |
| **Other voluntary information:** any voluntary information you may provide us in the course of your interactions with us (such as by sending an email through our Site and/or to the addresses indicated in our Site or by calling, emailing, texting, or chatting online with our customer service team and/or store staff, posting product reviews and ratings, or by responding to surveys or competitions) | From you | To handle your requests and to contact you when necessary or requested, including responding to your questions and comments and providing customer support; to improve our Site, customer service, and user experience | With related entities and with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.) |
| **Information automatically collected from your browser:** your browser type; operating system type or mobile device model, viewed webpages, links that are clicked, sponsored links or third-party advertisements that are clicked, keystrokes typed, movement of the mouse or pointer, IP address, mobile device identifier or other unique identifier, sites or apps visited before coming to our Site, the amount of time you spend viewing or using our Site, the number of times you return, or other click-stream or Site-usage data, and emails we send that you open, forward, or click through to our Site | From you and from our Site or app technology’s interaction with your browser or devices | To improve our Site, customer service, user experience, products and services; to create a session replay that shows your visit to our site; to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business, such as by protecting against and preventing fraud and unauthorized transactions, and managing risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users; and, in an aggregated nonspecific format, for analytical and demographic purposes | With related entities; with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.); and with your consent, with third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you |
| **Information automatically collected from your device and internet network:** your internet service provider, your internet protocol or IP address domain names of the computers you use to visit our Site, your operating system and browser used, and the type of handheld or mobile device used, such as laptop or smart phone, log files, URIs (Uniform Resource Identifiers) of the resources requested, the time of the request, the method used to submit the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in reply, the numerical status code of the server reply (successful, error, etc.) and other parameters concerning the user’s operating system and computer environment, and/or device cookie settings and other device details such as MAC address | From you and from our Site or app technology’s interaction with your browser or devices, and from service providers who support our fraud-detection efforts | To improve our Site, customer service, and user experience; to provide customer service; to make sure our Site and app technology work properly with your device and make sure you can see and use our intended Site and apps on the device you are using; for analytical and demographic purposes and to provide offers that may be of interest to you; to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business, such as by protecting against and preventing fraud and unauthorized transactions, and managing risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users | With related entities; with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.); and with your consent, with third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you |
| **Preference information:** such as your account settings, including preferred store, and your wish list, contact channel and types of services/offers that interest you | From you and from our Site or app technology’s interaction with your browser or devices and cookies tracking the pages you visit | To enhance your online shopping experience, including as a way to recognize you and welcome you to the Site; to personalize your experience; and to provide you with customized content | With related entities; with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.); and with your consent, with third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you |
| **Social media information:** if you interact with us through a social media service or log in using social media credentials, depending on your social media settings, we may have access to your information from that social network such as your ID, name, profile picture, email address, age range, gender, and location | From third parties, such as co-branded partners and websites (for example, on our Facebook pages) | For research, analytical, and other business purposes and to enhance your online shopping experience, including as a way to recognize you and welcome you to the Site and to provide you with customized content | With related entities; with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.); and with your consent, with third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you |
| **Sensitive personal information:** such as your driver’s license number, state identification card, precise geolocation (if you permit us to obtain your precise geolocation), your ethnic origin, and biometric data (limited); combination of email address, financial account, debit card, or credit card with security or access code, password, or other credentials allowing access to your account | From you (online and offline, such as in stores/in the course of using or processing online services or remote order/sales services, including chatting online with or otherwise contacting customer service) | To complete a particular transaction or fulfill a service; to check that the right person is using the right card or account. To provide offers that may be of interest to you, for analytical and demographic purposes, and to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business, such as by protecting against and preventing fraud and unauthorized transactions, and managing risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users | With related group entities; with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.); and with your consent, with third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you |
| **Accident information:** details about any accident or injury on our premises | From you and from witnesses | To get you the help you need; to assist emergency services; for insurance claims; to defend ourselves; and to prevent loss | With related entities; with law enforcement and other governmental authorities in accordance with applicable law; and with our professional advisors |
| **Legal information:** fraud checks or flags raised about your transactions, the payment card you want to use, payment card refusals, suspected crimes, complaints, claims and accidents | From you, the police crime and fraud-prevention agencies, payment card providers, the public, regulators, and your and our professional advisors and representatives | To protect you, other customers and our business against criminal activities and risks; to make sure that we understand and can meet our legal obligations to you and others, and can defend ourselves; and, if required by law, governmental request or court order, or based on our good-faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court order or to protect the users of our Site or the public | With related entities; with our service providers who help us with fraud protection and credit risk reduction; and with law enforcement and other governmental authorities in accordance with applicable law |
| **Inferences drawn from the information identified above:** to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes | From you and the other sources listed above | To enhance your online shopping experience; to personalize your experience; to provide you with customized content; and to better understand what product(s) interest our customers | With related entities; with certain authorized third parties for the purpose of providing specialized services to us (such as helping us to maintain and manage our customer information, communicate with our customers, service our Site, conduct promotions or surveys, fulfill orders, etc.); and with third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you |

In addition to the uses set forth above, Lands’ End may use and disclose the categories of personal information identified:

* To comply with applicable legal and regulatory requests and obligations (including investigations).
* To establish or defend legal claims and allegations.
* For security or the prevention, detection, or investigation of fraud, suspected or actual illegal activity, violations of company policy or rules, or other misconduct.
* To seek advice from lawyers, auditors, and other professional advisers.
* To respond to inquiries for a winners list, in the event you are the winner of a sweepstakes or other contest.
* In the process of a merger or acquisition, such as an asset sale, corporate reorganization, or other change of control.

**Cross-Border Transfer of Personal Information**

It is important to note that the Site is operated in the United States. Therefore, your personal information may be transferred to and stored in the United States or other countries with data protection laws that differ from the country where you are located. Your personal information may be available to government authorities under lawful orders and laws applicable in such foreign jurisdictions. By interacting with the Site and providing personal information to us, you consent to the transfer and storage of your personal information as described.

YOUR CHOICES AND PRIVACY RIGHTS:
--------------------------------

_(Residents of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, Virginia, and other states may have additional rights as described below in the section titled “Your California and Other State Privacy Rights.”)_

* **Catalogs**  
      
    Request to Receive Catalogs: If you would like to receive our catalogs, please call 1-800-963-4816 or [websiteinquiry@landsend.com](mailto:websiteinquiry@landsend.com). We will need your name, address, and telephone number to mail catalogs to you.  
      
    Request to Stop Catalogs: If you would like to stop receiving our catalogs, please call 1-800-963-4816 or email [websiteinquiry@landsend.com](mailto:websiteinquiry@landsend.com). It may take 2-4 weeks to process your request.
  
* **Request to Opt Out of Third-Party Marketing:** We may make portions of our catalog and email lists available to carefully screened companies whose products or services might interest you. If you prefer to have your name withheld from these lists, please call us at 1-800-963-4816 or email [websiteinquiry@landsend.com](mailto:websiteinquiry@landsend.com).
  
* **Postal Mail**  
      
    Lands’ End, Inc.  
    1 Lands’ End Lane  
    Dodgeville, Wisconsin 53595  
    1-800-963-4816
  
* **General Privacy Questions:** If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please use our Contact Us Form, call 1-800-963-4816 or send an email, including your name and mailing address, to [websiteinquiry@landsend.com](mailto:websiteinquiry@landsend.com).
  
* **Disabling Cookies**  
      
    Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them‚ blocking them‚ or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please look at your browser for instructions on this function. You can choose to browse our Site without accepting our Site’s cookies. These cookies allow us to recognize you from page to page‚ and they support your transactions with us. Without these cookies enabled‚ you may not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain Site features.
  
* **Internet-Based Advertising/Online Advertisements**  
      
    Lands’ End works with third-party service providers that help serve ads on our behalf on various online advertising networks. The online ad networks may use your browsing history across participating websites to show you interest-based advertisements on those websites. You may see ads for Lands’ End on participating websites based on how you browse our Site as well as how you browse those websites.  
      
    Lands’ End works with third party service providers who help serve ads on our behalf on various online advertising networks. The online ad networks may use your browsing history across participating websites to show you interest-based advertisements on those websites. You may see ads for Lands’ End on participating websites based on how you browse our Site as well as how you browse those websites.  
      
    To learn more about interest-based advertising‚ including how to opt out‚ visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). Please note that the opt-out mechanism relies on cookies to remember your choices with respect to ad-serving on websites. We may also use technologies‚ such as our own cookies‚ to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising‚ links are available on [LandsEnd.com](https://www.landsend.com/). Other websites you visit may offer their own opt-outs. If you do opt out of interest-based advertisements‚ you may still see advertisements on websites that you visit‚ but those ads will not be based on your browsing behavior. If you delete your cookies‚ use another computer or device‚ or change browsers‚ you will need to repeat the opt-out process.

**How You Access and Update Your Personal Information**

In order to keep your personal information accurate and complete, you can access or update some of it in the following ways:

* If you have created a [landsend.com](https://www.landsend.com/) account, you can log in to review and update your account information, including contact, billing, and shipping information.
* Call Customer Service at 1-800-963-4816 with your current contact information and the personal information you would like to access. We will provide you the personal information requested if reasonably available or will describe the types of personal information we typically collect.

### How Your Personal Information Is Protected

**Security Methods**

We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect your personal information. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit or debit card number, we use industry-standard methods to protect that information, and we are CPI complaint. However, no e-commerce solution, website, mobile application, database, or system is completely secure or “hacker proof.” You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse.

**Children’s Personal Information**

We recognize the importance of protecting privacy where children are involved. Lands’ End does not sell products for purchase by children, and all children’s products we sell are for purchase by adults only. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information online, we ask that a parent or guardian call Customer Service at 1-800-963-4816. We do not have actual knowledge about selling or sharing personal information of consumers under the age of 16.

**Notice of Financial Incentive**

We may offer financial incentives and/or price or service differences (“Incentives”) to participants in exchange for our use of your personal information.

To offer these Incentives, we must track the personal information you provide when you sign up or engage in activities in connection with our promotions, such as your email address and engagement with Lands’ End (“Lands’ End Data”).

The value of Lands’ End Data is calculated by determining the approximate additional spending per participant, per year compared to individuals who have not participated. The value of Lands’ End Data is reasonably related to the costs associated with offering the Incentives. You can join our mailing list and/or texting list on our Site, and you can withdraw from or cancel your registration at any time by removing yourself from mailing list and/or texting list on our Site or contact us at 1-800-746-3467.

**Retention Period**

We will retain your personal data for as long as needed or permitted in light of the purposes for which it was obtained. The criteria used to determine our retention periods include (a) the length of time we have an ongoing relationship with our Customers and provide services, (b) whether there is a legal obligation to which we are subject, and (c) whether retention is advisable in light of our legal position (such as in regard to applicable statutes of limitations, litigation or regulatory investigations).

Your California and Other State Privacy Rights
----------------------------------------------

If you are a resident of California or Virginia (starting Jan. 1, 2023), Colorado or Connecticut (starting July 1, 2023), or Utah (starting Dec. 31, 2023), the law in those states provides you with the following rights with respect to your personal information:

Your California Privacy Rights

* The right to know what personal information we have collected, used, disclosed, and sold about you, including the categories of personal information; the categories of sources from which the personal information is collected; the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing personal information; the categories of third parties to whom Lands’ End discloses personal information; and the specific pieces of personal information Lands’ End has collected about you.
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your personal information, taking into account the nature of the personal information and the purposes of the processing.
* The right to request that we delete any personal information that we have about you.
* The right to opt out of the selling or sharing of your personal information, which you can exercise through the [contact form](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy) available on our Site or by modifying your privacy preferences (e.g., Global Privacy Control), available through certain internet browsers and extensions, that signal your preference to opt out. Please note that clearing your cookies at any time will remove the signal of your selected privacy preferences.
* The right to limit the use of your sensitive personal information, which you can exercise through the [contact form](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy) available on our Site- if beyond what is necessary for providing goods and services.

To submit any of the above requests, you may contact us at 1-800-746-3467 or use the [contact form](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy) available on our Site. You may also designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf on our Site through our [contact form](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy). When you exercise these rights and submit a request to us, we will verify your identity by asking you to provide us with additional information such as your email address, order numbers of previous orders of our products and services, or the last four digits of a credit or debit card used to make a purchase or other means to verify your identity. We also may use a third-party verification provider to verify your identity. We will endeavor to honor such requests unless such a request conflicts with certain lawful exemptions under California’s consumer privacy law. Please note that we are only required to honor requests to know twice in a 12-month period.

We do not discriminate against California residents who exercise any of their rights described in our Privacy Policy. Your exercise of these rights will have no adverse effect on the price and quality of our goods or services.

In addition, and as set forth below, California law requires us to identify, for the 12-month period prior to the date of this Privacy Policy, what information we may have “sold” or “shared” about you. For the 12-month period prior to the date of this Privacy Policy, Lands’ End has only sold personal information about its customers as described above. For the 12-month period prior to the date of this Privacy Policy, Lands’ End has only shared personal information about its customers as described above. Lands’ End does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, as defined in applicable laws, for any purposes other than those permitted by applicable law.

**Opt-Out Preference Signals:** We are working toward enabling Global Privacy Control (GPC) as an additional way for you to submit a request to opt out of the sale and sharing of your personal information through browsers and/or browser extensions that support such a signal. Until then, you can opt out of the use of third-party cookies for personalized advertising by setting the cookie preferences on your browser.

This Privacy Policy describes how we may share your information for marketing purposes, as described above. If you are a California resident, the Shine the Light law permits you to request and obtain from us once per calendar year information about any of your personal information shared with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes, including the categories of information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we have shared such information. To request this information and for any other questions about our privacy practices and compliance with California law, please contact us through the [contact form](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy) on our Site.

Your Virginia (starting Jan. 1, 2023), Colorado (starting July 1, 2023), and Connecticut (starting July 1, 2023) Privacy Rights

* The right to confirm whether we process your personal information and access your personal information.
* The right to correct inaccuracies in your personal information, taking into account the nature of the personal information and the purposes of the processing.
* The right to delete personal information that we have about you.
* The right to opt out of the processing of your personal information for purposes of targeted advertising, the sale of personal information, and/or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.
* The right to obtain a copy of personal information we have obtained about you in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format.
* If we deny your request, the right to appeal our decision.

To submit any of the above requests, you may call us at 1-800-746-3467 or use the [contact form](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy) available on our Site. When you exercise these rights and submit a request to us, we will verify your identity by asking you to log in to your account if you have one with us. Or, if you do not, we may ask for your email address. We may also use a third-party verification provider to verify your identity. We will endeavor to honor such requests unless such a request conflicts with certain lawful exemptions under your state’s consumer privacy law.

The fact that you have elected to exercise these rights will have no adverse effect on the price and quality of our products or services.

To appeal a decision that we have made regarding your request, you may call us at 1-800-746-3467 or use the [contact form](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy) available on our Site. We will respond to appeals from Virginia and Connecticut residents within 60 days. We will respond to appeals from Colorado residents within 45 days.

Your Utah Privacy Rights (starting Dec. 31, 2023)

* The right to confirm whether we process your personal information and access your personal information.
* The right to delete personal information that we have about you.
* The right to opt out of the processing of your personal information for purposes of targeted advertising and/or the sale of personal information.
* The right to obtain a copy of the personal information you have previously provided to us in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format.

To submit any of the above requests, you may call us at 1-800-746-3467 or use the [contact form](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy) available on our Site. When you exercise these rights and submit a request to us, we will verify your identity by asking you to log in to your account if you have one with us. Or, if you do not, we may ask for your email address. We may also use a third-party verification provider to verify your identity. We will endeavor to honor such requests unless such a request conflicts with certain lawful exemptions under the Utah Privacy Rights Act.

The fact that you have elected to exercise these rights will have no adverse effect on the price and quality of our products or services.

**If you have any questions related to your state consumer privacy rights, please call 1-800-746-3467, Monday through Friday from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. Central Time.**

Nevada Residents
----------------

Nevada law gives Nevada consumers the right to request that a company not sell their personal information. This right applies even if their personal information is not currently being sold. If you are a Nevada consumer and wish to exercise this right, please submit your request by filling out the form at [www.landsend.com/customer-privacy](https://www.landsend.com/customer-privacy) or **call 1-800-746-3467, Monday through Friday from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. Central Time.**

Text Message Terms of Use
-------------------------

1. Your carrier’s standard messaging rates apply to your entry or submission message to any Lands’ End text message service, our confirmation, and all subsequent text message correspondence. Lands’ End does not charge for any content; however, downloadable content may incur additional charges from your cell phone provider. Please contact your wireless carrier for information about your messaging and data plan(s). Your carrier may impose message or charge limitations on your account that are outside our control. All associated charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider.
2. By subscribing to LANDS’ END ANYWHERE, you consent to receiving up to eight automated marketing text messages per month from Lands’ End at the mobile number provided at opt-in, which may include offers from us, our affiliates, and partners. You can unsubscribe at any time by texting STOP to 77344. Your consent to receive text messages is not a condition of purchase. Message and data rates may apply.
3. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device you use to subscribe to our text message service, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.
4. We will not be liable for any delays or failures in your receipt of any text messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator and processing by your mobile device. Carriers are not liable for delayed or failed messages. Our text message services are provided on an AS IS, AS AVAILABLE basis.
5. Data obtained from you in connection with our text message service may include your cell phone number, your carrier’s name, and the date, time, and content of your messages to us and other information that you may provide. We may use this information to contact you and to provide the services you request from us, and to otherwise operate, develop and improve the service. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your text usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies. We will only use information you provide to the service to transmit your text message or as otherwise described in our privacy policy. Nonetheless, we reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation, or governmental request; to avoid liability; or to protect our rights or property. When you complete forms online or otherwise provide us information in connection with the service, you agree to provide accurate, complete, and true information.
6. Our text message service and the content and materials provided through the service are proprietary to us or our licensors and are for your personal, noncommercial use only. You shall not damage, impair, interfere with, or disrupt the service or its functionality.
7. Our text message service is available only in the United States.
8. We reserve the right to alter these text message terms and conditions from time to time. We may suspend or terminate our text message service to you if we believe that you are in breach of our terms and conditions. Your service is also subject to termination if your wireless service terminates or lapses. If you change or deactivate your mobile number, it is your responsibility to notify Lands’ End by emailing us at [talkback@landsend.com](mailto:talkback@landsend.com). We may discontinue the service at any time.
9. If you have any questions, email us at [talkback@landsend.com](mailto:talkback@landsend.com). You can also text the word HELP to 77344 to get additional information about the service. We do not charge for help or info messages; however, your normal carrier rates apply.
10. Terms are subject to change.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

Lands’ End may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. We will also notify you of material changes either by email or by a notice on this Site. Your continued use of this Site following such changes demonstrates your consent to them.
